yugma.com 2008-05-10

# Yugma: Free Web Collaboration Forever — anytime, anywhere.

### Privacy Policy

By registering your details with us you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Service. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Yugma (http://www.Yugma.com), owned by Yugma, Inc. Because maintaining the trust of our users is a priority to us, Yugma is committed to respecting your privacy. Because Yugma wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by any interested parties. Yugma welcomes your feedback about this privacy policy. Send your questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement to [info@Yugma.com](mailto:info@yugma.com).

### Contents

  1. What is Yugma and why is my information needed? 
  2. What information does Yugma gather/track and how is it used? 
  3. With whom does Yugma share the information? 
  4. How can I review, correct and update my personal information?
  5. How can I opt out of Yugma's collection, use and distribution of my information?
  6. How does Yugma protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?
  7. Who can I ask if I have additional questions?

From time to time, Yugma may introduce new products and services. To the extent that these new products and services affect this policy, this policy will be updated. Please see item number 5 for more details.

### 1\. What is Yugma and why is my information needed?

Yugma is an online managed service that allows users to collaborate on documents, deliver presentations, perform product demonstrations, collaborate on shared documents and securely share confidential information from anywhere, anytime. Because Yugma is Web based, it requires the use of first and last names, billing contact information, a password and a valid email address as a login. Therefore, at a minimum, we require such necessary information during the registration process.

### 2\. What information does Yugmagather/track and how is it used?

PERSONAL INFORMATION: Because of the nature of our product, we must collect personal information from users during the registration process, including (at minimum) first and last names, an email address to be used as a login, billing contact information and a password. Your email address may be used to send you periodic newsletters from Yugma and it may be used by us on the behalf of third-party advertisers, but only upon your express consent.We use the information collected to deliver services, process payments, update our records, communicate with you about products and services and generally maintain your accounts with us.Yugma in-session information is end-to-end encrypted and only accessible by the authorized meeting organizer and participants. "In-session information" includes all screen sharing data, keyboard/mouse control data and text chat information. This information is never exposed in unencrypted form while temporarily resident within Yugma communication infrastructure servers or during transmission across public or private networks. Information about scheduled meetings and prior meetings such as subject, organizer name, and meeting time is stored on our website and is available to the meeting organizer and authenticated users that have received an invitation from the organizer via email, instant messenger, phone, or other communication method.Because of our commitment to present the best possible product to all our users, we track the category of services selected by our individual users as well as all information pertaining to user satisfaction. To ensure the quality of our product, we reserve the right to maintain evaluation and feedback records.

BUSINESS INFORMATION: Information that is provided by meeting organizers or administrators such as meeting schedules, attendee lists (participant name, email address and any other business contact information requested by the meeting organizer) and meeting subject name is considered confidential to the purchaser or co-sponsor of the meeting event. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit while in-session and utilizing the chat feature can be read, collected or used by the meeting organizer and other meeting participants. We will not view Business Information except as necessary to appropriately support the service. We will only use the Business Information provided for the purpose of anticipating, diagnosing, supporting or resolving any problems that might limit or disrupt the quality of your Yugma experience.

PARTNERS: In some cases we provide services or sell product lines jointly with other businesses. For these co-branded offerings in which a third party is involved in your transactions, we will sometimes share or jointly collect customer information related to those transactions with that third party. On the co-branded registration pages we will state who is collecting or receiving the information and whose privacy statement governs its use so that you will know at the time you create your account exactly how your information will be used. If you are registered with Yugma through a partnership and you request to opt out of receiving promotional updates, in order to comply with the provisions in the Can Spam Act, we will also provide your email address to that partner so that they may also discontinue sending you messages on behalf of Yugma.

SESSION RECORDS: To maintain our quality of service and to assist in the analysis of product performance, we may also gather data on connection information, including the timing and size of all packets sent over the Internet during a session. The gathered information is used only to ensure the highest quality experience possible at Yugma.

SECURITY INFORMATION: Yugma also collects certain standard information about your computer for security and identification purposes. This information may include: IP addresses, domain names, access times, cookies, and other uniquely identifying information of machines that have the Yugma software downloaded and installed. This information is used for the operation of the service, to identify and protect our customers and to control unauthorized use or abuse of our services. All information is encrypted during transmission and is stored securely within our servers.

SURVEYS: In addition to required member information, we may conduct surveys and ask users to volunteer demographic information to be used on an aggregate basis for internal market research, presentation to advertisers and joint research projects with outside companies involved in product development. We use such information to better focus our product and personalize the scope of services offered to each individual user. Such information will not be passed to third parties without your prior consent unless where required by applicable law.

TRAFFIC PATTERNS: We also track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our site. However, we do not correlate this information with personally identifiable data about individual users. We do track domain names, browser types and MIME type. Such information will not be passed to third parties without your prior consent unless where required by applicable law.

COOKIES: A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns and hold certain registration information. When registering at Yugma sites, we use cookies to store unique, randomly assigned user IDs that we generate for administrative purposes. These cookies enable you to enter the Yugma sites without having to log on each time. We do not store passwords or any personally identifiable information about you in the cookies.Yugma also partners with selected marketing companies to help us track the effectiveness of our Web site, generate visitor traffic. When a partner refers a visitor to us from any of these sites, they set a Web beacon and a cookie on our site. An ad ID and a partner ID are stored in the cookie, but no personally identifiable information specific to the actual visitor is stored. Yugma does not see the cookie; we only include the Web beacon on our page, which results in a request to the partner's servers from the customer browser. We have no control over their use of the cookie after it is placed on our site.Yugma is not responsible for the information collected in these cookies, nor do we host the reporting and tracking of the profile information. The profiles contain information about browser versions, operating systems, screen resolutions and what content, products and services you look at when visiting our site.The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. You can still review the Web site if you choose to set your browser to refuse all cookies; however, you must enable cookies in order to establish an account and to download and install the Yugma software.

### 3\. With whom does Yugmashare the information?

Yugma products and services by necessity require us to provide some of your information to third parties. We may occasionally employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, sending postal mail and email, analyzing data and providing marketing assistance. They have access to personal information needed only to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Further, they must process the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Also, in the event that Yugma or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. For more information see Section 5 below.Occasionally we send offers to select groups of Yugma customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not share your personal information with the other businesses. Except in the limited instances as stated above, we will never voluntarily share personally identifiable information with any third party without the user's express consent or unless compelled by applicable state and federal laws.Yugma does not control the practices of our affiliates. If you have questions about how affiliates use the information gathered when you link to them, please read their privacy policies.

### 4\. How can I review, correct and update my personal information?

If you wish to change your personal information, go to your My Account page where you can change your user name, email address and password, as well as update your credit card and billing information. You can also change your email subscription status to receive our newsletter, email marketing communications and third-party promotions administered by Yugma.

### 5\. How can I opt out of Yugma'collection, use and distribution of my information?

To change your email subscription status to receive or to stop receiving marketing communications or third-party promotions administered by Yugma or to opt out of Yugma's collection, use and distribution of your information as stated above, please go to the Unsubscribe page, enter your email address and then click Submit. This privacy policy is subject to change. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not you consent to the usage of your information in a different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change.

### 6\. How does Yugmaprotect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?

Yugma uses industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of personally identifiable information, including encryption, firewalls and SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). Furthermore, Yugma is not liable for loss of passwords due to user carelessness. If you lose control over your password, you may lose control over your personally identifiable information. If you believe your password has been compromised, we recommend that you immediately change your password. For information on how to do this, please see item number 4 above.

### 7\. Who can I ask if I have additional questions?

For additional inquiries about the privacy of your information, you can contact Yugma via email at  
[info@yugma.com](mailto:info@yugma.com), by calling +1-952-400-0357 or by writing to us via regular mail at: Yugma, 5700 Smetana Drive, Suite 100, Minneapolis, MN 55343. To reach our Customer support department, you may contact us at [support@yugma.com](mailto:support@yugma.com).
